Just take a look.
한 번 보세요.
Show tonight
오늘 밤에 보여줘
Sitting there alone.
거기 혼자 앉아 있어요.
Never had contact with anyone.
누구와도 접촉한 적이 없습니다.
Someone must have touched the glass.
누군가가 유리를 만졌나 봐요.
But the bartenders and waiters
하지만 바텐더와 웨이터는
has been checked.
확인되었습니다.
There are no suspects.
용의자는 없습니다.
I think it's possible for everyone
누구나 가능하다고 생각해요
There are too many people in the bar tonight.
오늘 밤 바에는 사람이 너무 많아요.
My eyes were almost blurry.
내 눈은 거의 흐릿했다.
wait.
기다리다.
possible.
가능한.
enlarge.
크게 하다.
Zoom in a little bit and I get it.
조금 확대하면 알 수 있습니다.
what have you found?
무엇을 찾았나요?
Look what's in the glass.
유리 안에 무엇이 있는지보세요.
In glass?
유리에?
Batu.
바투.
Investigate this woman.
이 여자를 조사해 보세요.
In front of and behind this woman.
이 여자의 앞과 뒤.
Screenshot of Fang Lu’s glasses.
Fang Lu의 안경 스크린샷.
OK
좋아요
Did you see that?
그거 봤어?
hockey in glass
유리 속의 하키
Sizes vary.
크기는 다양합니다.
During this process,
이 과정에서,
Never touch the beer glass.
맥주잔은 절대 만지지 마세요.
You see the glass in his hand.
그의 손에 유리잔이 보입니다.
He is there.
그는 거기에 있습니다.
He replaced the glass.
그는 유리를 교체했습니다.
He also covered the CCTV with his body.
CCTV도 온몸으로 가렸다.
I can't record it.
녹음할 수 없어요.
find out
알아내다
[This woman. ]
[이 여자. ]
See if there are any front-facing screenshots.
전면 스크린샷이 있는지 확인하세요.
This seems to be
이 것 같다
he is very familiar
그는 매우 친숙하다
In this CCTV environment.
이 CCTV 환경에서는.
So always avoid it deliberately.
그러므로 항상 의도적으로 피하십시오.
we can't get
우리는 얻을 수 없습니다
Positive video.
긍정적인 영상.
He is a veteran. what do you think?
그는 베테랑입니다. 어떻게 생각하나요?
This figure
이 그림
Something familiar.
익숙한 것.
Is it Chen Ting?
첸팅인가?
We compared them.
우리는 그것들을 비교했습니다.
not him.
그는 아니고.
The lights are too dim.
조명이 너무 어둡습니다.
I can't see clearly.
나는 명확하게 볼 수 없습니다.
Happy birthday.
생일 축하해요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
welcome.
환영.
are you alone?
너 혼자야?
Myself.
내 자신.
here.
여기.
I'll give you some water.
물 좀 드릴께요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
enough.
충분한.
Ayo.
아요.
Give us money.
우리에게 돈을 주세요.
OK
좋아요
Until it was discovered.
그것이 발견될 때까지.
enough.
충분한.
great.
엄청난.
Let's go drink somewhere else.
다른 데 가서 마시자.
Ayo.
아요.
Visitors from the industrial park opposite
맞은편 산업단지에서 온 방문객들
It comes almost every day.
거의 매일 옵니다.
Why are these hands so cold?
이 손은 왜 이렇게 차가워?
Lower body temperature.
체온을 낮추십시오.
what's on your mind?
무슨 생각 중이야?
unconcentrated.
집중되지 않은.
I am fine.
괜찮아요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Just make up for it
그냥 만회해
OK
좋아요
Scan first.
먼저 스캔하세요.
look.
바라보다.
how much does it cost?
비용이 얼마나 드나요?
I'll tell you after I think about it.
생각해보고 말씀드리겠습니다.
What do you want to eat?
너 뭐 먹고 싶니?
I just ordered a bowl of noodles.
방금 국수 한 그릇을 주문했어요.
my stove.
내 난로.
Yes.
예.
Sister, Teacher Gao has gone home from get off work.
언니, 가오 선생님이 퇴근하고 집에 가셨어요.
let me.
허락해 주세요.
Thanks.
감사해요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I am fine.
괜찮아요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
Just make up for it
그냥 만회해
Thanks.
감사해요.
Nowadays, not only are there heart problems;
요즘에는 심장 문제만 있는 것이 아닙니다.
But also very quiet.
그러나 또한 매우 조용합니다.
Maybe he's tired.
아마도 그는 피곤했을 것입니다.
My job was not going well.
내 일은 잘 되지 않았다.
A bit troublesome.
조금 귀찮습니다.
Can you work it out with me?
나와 함께 해결할 수 있나요?
If you can't,
당신이 할 수 없다면,
Leave the problem till tomorrow.
문제는 내일까지 남겨두세요.
Don't think about it just yet.
아직 그것에 대해 생각하지 마십시오.
make sense.
말이 되네요.
Our new products.
우리의 새로운 제품.
Not sweet dessert, give it a try.
달콤한 디저트는 아니니 꼭 드셔보세요.
Please your mood.
당신의 기분을 부탁드립니다.
I...
나...
Don't reject me.
나를 거부하지 마십시오.
OK, I'll try it.
알겠습니다. 시도해 보겠습니다.
Will you remember all the details?
모든 세부 사항을 기억할 수 있나요?
I remember all customers' preferences.
나는 고객의 취향을 모두 기억합니다.
Is this an occupational disease?
직업병인가요?
Not a job.
직업이 아닙니다.
Available to a limited number of guests only.
제한된 수의 손님에게만 제공됩니다.
You are a little different today.
오늘 당신은 조금 다릅니다.
what is the difference?
차이점은 무엇입니까?
It feels different.
느낌이 다릅니다.
Is it because
때문인가?
Drank too much?
너무 많이 마셨나요?
Guest birthday.
손님 생일.
I had a few more drinks.
나는 몇 잔 더 마셨다.
No wonder.
당연합니다.
Is it so clear?
너무 명확합니까?
reasonable.
합리적인.
What else do you want to eat?
또 무엇을 먹고 싶나요?
Enough, no need.
충분합니다. 필요하지 않습니다.
In fact, today,
사실 오늘은,
After leaving the company, I wanted to come here.
회사를 그만두고 여기로 오고 싶었어요.
See you're not here.
보세요, 당신은 여기 없어요.
when?
언제?
Around 19 o'clock.
19시쯤.
No way, I'm always here.
안돼요, 난 항상 여기 있어요.
is this real?
이거 진짜야?
Have you entered?
입장하셨나요?
No.
아니요.
I noticed you weren't at the door.
나는 당신이 문 앞에 없는 것을 알아차렸습니다.
It happens that the company
회사에서 그런 일이 일어나요
He called me and said he wanted to work overtime.
그는 나에게 전화해서 초과 근무를 하고 싶다고 말했습니다.
So I didn't go in.
그래서 나는 들어가지 않았다.
Maybe I'm busy in the kitchen,
아마도 주방에서 바빠서 그럴지도 모르겠습니다.
Or go to the toilet.
아니면 화장실에 가세요.
perhaps.
아마도.
You wouldn't have come in without me.
나 없이는 너도 들어오지 못했을 거야.
you are here to eat
당신은 식사하러 왔습니다
Or find me?
아니면 나를 찾아?
I just love your cooking.
나는 단지 당신의 요리를 좋아합니다.
That's fine if you like it.
당신이 그것을 좋아한다면 괜찮습니다.
But this customer,
그런데 이 고객님,
We're almost closing too.
우리도 거의 문을 닫고 있어요.
sorry,
죄송합니다,
Your time has been wasted.
당신의 시간은 낭비되었습니다.
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
If so, I'll pay.
그렇다면 지불하겠습니다.
Okay, I'll go first.
알았어, 나 먼저 갈게.
Until it was discovered.
그것이 발견될 때까지.
this dessert
이 디저트
reasonable.
합리적인.
Did he come at 19 o'clock?
19시에 왔나요?
19 o'clock?
19시?
I was in the kitchen at that time,
나는 그 시간에 부엌에 있었고,
Didn't pay attention outside.
밖에는 관심을 두지 않았습니다.
Why?
왜?
It doesn't taste very good.
맛이 별로 좋지 않아요.
Stone, how about it?
스톤, 어때요?
Didn't notice he was gone.
그가 사라진 것을 눈치 채지 못했습니다.
Gao Tianyang came to the store today.
오늘 Gao Tianyang이 가게에 왔습니다.
He tested me on purpose.
그는 일부러 나를 시험했습니다.
Are you too close?
너무 가깝나요?
What are you afraid of?
당신은 무엇을 두려워합니까?
Dia Guk-an.
다이아국안.
He is no ordinary mission target.
그는 평범한 임무 대상이 아닙니다.
You will expose yourself.
당신은 자신을 드러내게 될 것입니다.
You worry about my abilities
내 능력을 걱정하는구나
Or is it my charm?
아니면 나의 매력인가?
it depends on how big it is
그것은 그것이 얼마나 큰가에 달려있다.
Some of your energy is on it.
당신의 에너지 중 일부가 그것에 있습니다.
Gao Tianyang is a big fish.
Gao Tianyang은 큰 물고기입니다.
This is no exaggeration.
이것은 과장이 아닙니다.
You quite like him
당신은 그 사람을 꽤 좋아해요
No.
아니요.
How can you get his attention?
어떻게 그의 관심을 끌 수 있습니까?
Yes.
예.
Don't overdo it.
과용하지 마십시오.
I know the limits.
나는 한계를 알고 있습니다.
How was yesterday?
어제는 어땠 니?
What?
무엇?
Didn't you go to the bar?
바에 가지 않았나요?
is it him?
그 사람이야?
The body posture is almost the same.
몸의 자세는 거의 같습니다.
but movement
하지만 움직임
The difference is quite big.
그 차이는 꽤 크다.
Experts can cover
전문가가 다룰 수 있음
Habits and actions.
습관과 행동.
I've tested it.
나는 그것을 테스트했습니다.
No vulnerabilities were found either.
취약점도 발견되지 않았습니다.
I'll ask Batu to check it out.
바투에게 확인해 보도록 할게요.
There are CCTV around.
주변에 CCTV가 있어요.
From 19:00 to 09:00,
19:00부터 09:00까지,
He didn't leave the bar either.
그 역시 바를 떠나지 않았다.
The CCTV in the bar was very blurry.
바의 CCTV는 매우 흐릿했습니다.
I found nothing.
나는 아무것도 찾지 못했습니다.
useful information.
유용한 정보.
so you
그래서 당신은
You can only rely on your own feelings.
당신은 자신의 감정에만 의존할 수 있습니다.
You must be disappointed.
당신은 실망해야합니다.
Not that easy.
그렇게 쉽지는 않습니다.
found it?
그것을 발견?
Submitted by Chen Ting
에 의해 제출 된 Chen Ting
Flight tomorrow morning.
내일 아침 비행기.
Fly to Paris.
파리로 날아가세요.
tomorrow.
내일.
Fang Lu is already like this,
Fang Lu는 이미 이렇습니다.
How do you go?
어떻게 가나요?
he submitted
그는 제출했다
Patient exit route.
환자 퇴원 경로.
Enter.
입력하다.
Chief Qin.
진 수석.
Sudden problems.
갑작스러운 문제.
Chen Ting wanted to leave with Fang Lu.
Chen Ting은 Fang Lu와 함께 떠나고 싶었습니다.
Go to Paris.
파리로 가세요.
Judging from the current situation,
현재 상황으로 판단해보면,
Chen Ting left with Fang Lu,
Chen Ting은 Fang Lu와 함께 떠났습니다.
he wants to continue
그 사람은 계속하고 싶어해
mengancam Fang Yongping.
Mengancam Fang Yongping.
He destroyed the evidence,
증거를 인멸했고,
Let Fang Lu faint.
Fang Lu를 기절시키세요.
It was all planned.
그것은 모두 계획된 일이었습니다.
We must act now.
우리는 지금 행동해야 합니다.
Tahan Chen Ting.
타한 첸 팅.
Don't let him get away.
그를 도망가게 하지 마세요.
Proof that he had been a spy.
그가 스파이였다는 증거.
almost.
거의.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
He can't run away.
그는 도망칠 수 없습니다.
most important goal
가장 중요한 목표
adalah Fang Yongping.
아달라 팡 용핑.
So far,
지금까지,
we should also
우리도 그래야 한다
dengan Fang Yongping.
팡용핑(Fang Yongping).
He is the leader of this city.
그는 이 도시의 지도자이다.
My son did it again.
내 아들이 또 그랬어요.
He must have suffered a lot.
그 사람도 많이 겪었을 텐데요.
me and her
나와 그녀
There is no connection.
연결이 없습니다.
I definitely know him.
나는 그를 확실히 알고 있습니다.
He is not
그는 아니다
Very greedy person.
욕심이 많은 사람.
I want to talk to him.
나는 그와 이야기하고 싶다.
Qin.
진.
Mayor Fang.
팡 시장님.
You see I came uninvited.
내가 초대받지 않고 왔다는 걸 알잖아요.
It was a bit sudden.
좀 갑작스러웠어요.
It had become stuck in front of the house.
집앞에 막혀버렸습니다.
There are several possible situations
여러 가지 가능한 상황이 있습니다
You don't know yet.
당신은 아직 모른다.
Can we go in and talk?
우리 들어가서 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
Come in.
올.
I still remember you.
나는 아직도 당신을 기억합니다.
My favorite drink is Pu'er.
제가 가장 좋아하는 음료는 푸얼(Pu'er)입니다.
Many years of habit,
다년간의 습관,
It's hard to change.
변화하는 것은 어렵습니다.
Ayo.
아요.
Qin.
진.
in my memory,
내 기억 속에는
After going to Guoan
궈안에 다녀온 후
It seems this is our first time
이번이 처음인 것 같아요
Meet in person.
직접 만나보세요.
So today I came suddenly
그래서 오늘 갑자기 왔어
Definitely not for nostalgia.
확실히 향수를 불러일으키기 위한 것은 아닙니다.
if anything happens
무슨 일이 생기면
Just say it.
그냥 말해.
Let’s stop beating around the bush.
덤불 주위를 두드리는 것을 멈추자.
How is Fang Lu doing now?
팡루는 지금 어떻게 지내고 있나요?
Not in good condition.
상태가 좋지 않습니다.
I've been thinking lately,
최근에 생각해봤는데,
Send abroad.
해외로 보내세요.
Continue treatment.
치료를 계속하십시오.
we have already started
우리는 이미 시작했어요
The issue of Fang Lu’s murder,
방루 살해 문제,
Fang Lu’s case.
Fang Lu의 사례.
for a while he was scared
한동안 그는 무서웠어요
Can't leave Jinhai.
진하이를 떠날 수 없어요.
investigation?
조사?
Is he involved in the case?
그 사람이 사건에 연루되어 있나요?
We suspect he was involved
우리는 그가 연루된 것으로 의심합니다
So-called special forces missions.
소위 특수부대 임무.
Suspect.
의심하다.
Just doubtful.
의심 스럽습니다.
If there is no definite evidence,
확실한 증거가 없다면,
Thus restricting Fang Lu overseas.
따라서 Fang Lu를 해외로 제한합니다.
and continue treatment as normal.
정상적으로 치료를 계속합니다.
I don't think this is true.
나는 이것이 사실이 아니라고 생각합니다.
how do you know?
어떻게 알아?
We have no evidence.
증거가 없습니다.
if you have evidence
증거가 있다면
you should not
당신은해야하지
use this method
이 방법을 사용하세요
talk to me.
나에게 말을 걸어보세요.
Anda dan Fang Lu, Zheng Guoxian.
그리고 Fang Lu, Zheng Guoxian.
This is very relevant to you.
이것은 당신과 매우 관련이 있습니다.
I just learned about the situation.
방금 상황을 알게 됐어요.
Where is Zheng Guoxian?
Zheng Guoxian은 어디에 있나요?
I've already explained
나는 이미 설명했다.
To the organization.
조직에.
Surrender will not
항복은 하지 않을 것이다
for this case.
이 경우.
through further research
추가 연구를 통해
From Zheng Guoxian,
정궈시안(Zheng Guoxian)으로부터,
will realize that there are many things
많은 것들이 있다는 것을 깨닫게 될 것이다
unsolvable
해결할 수 없는
With your own strength.
자신의 힘으로.
So now we suspect
이제 우리는 의심한다
behind
뒤에
behind.
뒤에.
stronger person
더 강한 사람
from him.
그로부터.
they have already started
그들은 이미 시작했어
Discharge procedures.
퇴원 절차.
I already
이미 나는
Hospital.
병원.
Awasi Chen Ting.
아와시 첸 팅.
don't let him
그를 허락하지 마세요
Fang Lu was taken away.
Fang Lu는 제거되었습니다.
understand.
이해하다.
Aura.
영기.
Halo?
후광?
sorry.
죄송합니다.
our system
우리 시스템
Will be upgraded soon.
곧 업그레이드될 예정입니다.
Can you
할 수 있나요
[after? ]
[후에? ]
how long?
얼마나 오래?
soon.
곧.
Sit there and wait for a while.
거기 앉아서 잠시 기다리세요.
I'll call you when I'm done.
끝나면 전화할게요.
Incidentally,
그런데,
We work together.
우리는 같이 일한다.
Pu Quan.
푸콴.
do you remember?
기억 나니?
of.
의.
He was not then
그때는 그 사람이 아니었어
Go to the Provincial Military District?
성군구로 가시나요?
I met him last year.
나는 작년에 그를 만났습니다.
In the interrogation room.
심문실에서.
impossible.
불가능한.
Judging from his age, he should...
나이로 볼 때 그 사람은...
It must be returned.
반드시 반환되어야 합니다.
detail,
세부 사항,
I really can't tell you.
나는 정말로 당신에게 말할 수 없습니다.
But I can tell you,
하지만 내가 말할 수 있는 건,
He did so.
그는 그렇게 했습니다.
It's been several years.
몇 년이 지났습니다.
It's just that I haven't discovered it before.
단지 내가 이전에 그것을 발견하지 못했을 뿐입니다.
I remember before we talked about him
우리가 그 사람에 대해 이야기하기 전에 기억나네요
coward,
겁쟁이,
There is a reason for this.
여기에는 이유가 있습니다.
This kind of psychological burden
이런 심리적 부담이
Too heavy.
너무 무거워.
I am very touched.
나는 매우 감동 받았습니다.
He came in and told me,
그가 들어와서 나에게 말했다.
After he entered.
그가 들어간 후.
he just felt it
그 사람은 방금 그걸 느꼈어
Even relieved.
심지어 안심했다.
the most difficult
가장 어려운
in reality
실제로는
Exciting days.
신나는 날들.
Because everyone knows
모두가 알고 있으니까
If you do a few things,
몇 가지만 해보면,
It will definitely leave a mark.
분명 흔적이 남을 것입니다.
It's like when you're facing a crisis,
위기에 처했을 때와 같습니다.
When you face a crisis.
위기에 직면했을 때.
You absolutely understand.
당신은 절대적으로 이해합니다.
Who are you
누구세요
What does it imply to me?
그것은 나에게 무엇을 의미합니까?
No.
아니요.
I'm explaining.
설명하고 있어요.
Mayor Fang.
팡 시장님.
I hope you will turn yourself in.
나는 당신이 스스로를 제출하기를 바랍니다.
we doubt
우리는 의심한다
Chen Ting dari Yunyi Group
Chen Ting dari Yunyi 그룹
Ties to espionage organizations.
간첩조직과 연관되어 있습니다.
As for you and Fang Lu,
당신과 Fang Lu는
There are relationships
관계가 있습니다
With Chen Ting.
첸팅과 함께.
Because of Fang Lu’s overseas account
Fang Lu의 해외 계정 때문에
dan Chen Ting
단 첸 팅
With Chen Ting.
첸팅과 함께.
We have
우리는
this information.
이 정보.
and reported to superiors.
그리고 상급자에게 보고했다.
At a moment like this, do you ever think,
이런 순간, 이런 생각을 해본 적 있으신가요?
Can Fang Lu
칸 팡 루
Leave Jinhai?
진하이를 떠나시겠습니까?
I know my son.
나는 내 아들을 알고 있습니다.
he must be
그는 반드시
Be exploited.
착취 당하십시오.
Who manages overseas accounts?
해외계좌는 누가 관리하나요?
Mayor Fang.
팡 시장님.
I understand you.
나는 당신을 이해합니다.
You are not a greedy person.
당신은 탐욕스러운 사람이 아닙니다.
From union to regional director,
노조에서 지역이사로,
From regional leaders to mayors,
지역 지도자부터 시장까지,
You have a lot of opportunities for corruption.
부패할 가능성이 많습니다.
if you do it for money
돈 때문에 그런 짓을 한다면
Neither can you
당신도 마찬가지다
Gain appreciation from leaders.
지도자들로부터 감사를 얻으십시오.
so what?
그래서 뭐?
You must be in trouble.
당신은 곤경에 처해 있습니다.
Forced suffering?
강제적인 고통?
If not, you wouldn't do it.
그렇지 않다면, 당신은 그것을 하지 않을 것입니다.
You don't even have the courage to call the police
경찰에 신고할 용기도 없잖아
You don’t even dare to call the police.
감히 경찰에 신고할 엄두도 내지 못합니다.
Mayor Fang.
팡 시장님.
You are a smart person.
당신은 똑똑한 사람입니다.
And the best one can weigh the pros and cons.
그리고 가장 좋은 것은 장단점을 따질 수 있습니다.
If you really want to protect that child
정말로 그 아이를 지키고 싶다면
The best thing you can do now
지금 당신이 할 수 있는 가장 좋은 일은
Just keep it in the country.
그냥 국내에 보관하세요.
As soon as he comes out,
그 사람 나오자마자,
This will be
이것은 ~이 될 것이다
Someone else’s hostage.
다른 사람의 인질.
You are so useless
넌 정말 쓸모없어
Combating foreign espionage organizations.
외국 간첩 조직과의 싸움.
You feel
기분이
Can you live well?
잘 살 수 있나요?
worst decision
최악의 결정
in my life
내 인생에서
Just let my son go abroad.
내 아들을 해외로 보내주세요.
I think
제 생각에는
so,
그래서,
He will become more independent.
그는 더욱 독립적이 될 것입니다.
I can also focus.
집중도 할 수 있어요.
My own business.
내 자신의 경력.
i never thought
난 생각도 못했어
will hate me.
나를 싫어할 것이다.
More unexpected
더 예상치 못한
foreign espionage organization
외국 간첩 조직
will attack him.
그를 공격할 것이다.
Come threaten me.
와서 협박해.
I want to save the child.
나는 그 아이를 구하고 싶다.
There is no other choice.
다른 옵션은 없습니다.
But if I take this step
하지만 내가 이 단계를 밟으면
I can never go back.
나는 결코 돌아갈 수 없습니다.
I know their ways.
나는 그들의 방식을 알고 있습니다.
You are a coward.
당신은 겁쟁이입니다.
They are a group of animals.
그들은 동물 그룹입니다.
What I'm most worried about now is
지금 가장 걱정되는 건
It's my son
내 아들이야
Ultimately, whether you realize it or not.
결국, 당신이 깨닫든 깨닫지 못하든.
So your best option is now
따라서 최선의 선택은 지금입니다
is to work with us.
우리와 함께 일하는 것입니다.
you can confirm my child
내 아이를 확인할 수 있어요
Absolutely safe.
절대적으로 안전합니다.
really.
정말.
He went out.
그는 나갔어.
Hospital West Front.
병원 서쪽 앞.
Chen Ting.
첸 팅.
We doubt you now
우리는 지금 당신을 의심합니다
You are involved in an espionage operation.
당신은 간첩 작전에 연루되었습니다.
Please cooperate with our research.
저희 연구에 협조해 주시기 바랍니다.
you sure?
확실해요?
they absolutely can
그들은 절대적으로 할 수 있습니다
Fang Lu.
팡 루.
I have already contacted
이미 연락했어요
Experts from Jinhae Third Hospital.
진해제3병원 전문가들입니다.
Ask for directions.
방향을 묻다.
You just need to calm down.
진정하면됩니다.
Fang Lu should be coming soon
Fang Lu가 곧 올 것입니다.
will wake up
깨어날 것이다
Can I
내가 할 수 있을까?
go ahead
어서
See him again.
그를 다시 만나세요.
If not, maybe
그렇지 않다면 아마도
Won't meet again.
다시는 만나지 않을 것입니다.
this...
이것...
I really can't make a decision.
정말 결정을 내릴 수 없어요.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
this building
이 건물
very beautiful.
매우 아름답습니다.
of.
의.
Ten years ago, things were still peaceful here.
10년 전만 해도 이곳은 여전히 ​​평화로웠습니다.
I still remember you.
나는 아직도 당신을 기억합니다.
When he became district chief,
그가 지역 이장이 되었을 때,
Build this new city of the future.
미래의 새로운 도시를 건설해 보세요.
Now it has become
이제는 되었다
simbol Jinhai.
심볼 진하이.
i have done it
내가 해냈어
Many good decisions.
많은 좋은 결정.
But as long as you make a wrong decision,
하지만 잘못된 결정을 내리는 한,
Everything is wrong.
모두 잘못 됐어.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Hurry, hurry to the hospital. quickly.
서둘러요, 서둘러 병원으로 가세요. 빠르게.
OK
좋아요
how?
어떻게?
hold onto.
붙잡아라.
Yongping, hold on.
용핑, 잠깐만요.
No big deal.
별거 아니야.
All physical indicators are also normal.
모든 신체 지표도 정상입니다.
Pay attention to rest.
휴식에 주의하세요.
OK
좋아요
Where is Fang Lu?
팡루는 어디에 있나요?
I just saw it.
방금 봤어요.
He woke up.
그는 일어났다.
The doctor said
의사가 말했다.
He's fine.
그는 괜찮아.
It's very close.
매우 가깝습니다.
even though
~ 일지라도
See it from a distance,
멀리서 봐도,
Then we leave.
그런 다음 우리는 떠납니다.
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
I am fine.
괜찮아요.
My legs are a little weak.
다리가 좀 약해요.
Can't stand up anymore
더 이상 일어서지 못해요
His fever is gone.
그의 열이 사라졌습니다.
time flies.
시간은 흐른다.
instantly,
곧,
My son is 30 years old.
제 아들은 30세입니다.
Recently,
최근에,
I thought about it seriously.
나는 그것에 대해 진지하게 생각했다.
the two of us
우리 둘
Can think of it again
다시 생각해봐도 돼
A warm and happy time.
따뜻하고 행복한 시간.
At least.
적어도.
You know yourself well enough.
당신은 자신을 충분히 잘 알고 있습니다.
Since childhood,
어린 시절부터,
your relationship with dad
아빠와의 관계
Not that close.
그렇게 가깝지는 않습니다.
So I think,
그래서 나는 생각한다,
i must succeed
나는 성공해야 해
success.
성공.
I must
나는 해야 한다
For my son.
내 아들을 위해.
But Dad failed.
하지만 아빠는 실패했어요.
you are right.
당신 말이 맞아요.
If you come back,
당신이 돌아오면,
Dad will take you there
아빠가 거기까지 데려다줄게
Surrender to the organization.
조직에 항복하세요.
Explain this to the organization.
이를 조직에 설명하십시오.
The problem will not develop
문제가 발전하지 않을 것입니다
Like today.
오늘 같이.
Who can't come back today.
오늘은 누가 돌아올 수 없나요?
Dad was wrong.
아빠가 틀렸어요.
But I believe you.
하지만 나는 당신을 믿습니다.
I believe in my son
나는 내 아들을 믿는다
marvelous.
기이.
you must follow
당신은 따라야합니다
My own opinion,
나만의 의견,
walking on the road
길을 걷다
healthy.
건강한.
You have a responsibility.
당신에게는 책임이 있습니다.
responsible.
책임이 있는.
Dad, don't worry.
아빠, 걱정하지 마세요.
this time,
이 시간,
I can do it myself.
내 스스로 할 수있어.
leave.
떠나다.
I still have to take care of it
아직은 챙겨야 해
other things.
다른 것들.
Embrace.
포옹하다.
OK
좋아요
I go first.
내가 먼저 간다.
Batu.
바투.
Check.
확인하다.
OK
좋아요
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
This was found at Fang Yongping’s house
이것은 Fang Yongping의 집에서 발견되었습니다.
di rumah Fang Yongping.
디 루마 Fang Yongping.
in the deer head's eyes
사슴 머리의 눈 속에
In the eyes of a deer.
사슴의 눈으로.
I checked
나는 확인했다
from this surveillance camera.
이 감시 카메라에서요.
Disconnected.
연결이 끊어졌습니다.
Access this security camera.
이 보안 카메라에 접속하세요.
night fog
밤안개
Continue past this place.
이 곳을 지나 계속 가세요.
mengawasi Fang Yongping.
멘가와시 팡용핑.
Regarding Fang Lu’s research,
Fang Lu의 연구에 관해,
Also found here.
여기에서도 발견되었습니다.
They told me to take advantage of the investment business
투자사업을 이용하라고 하더군요
getting information
정보 얻기
and get information.
그리고 정보를 얻으세요.
provide information.
정보를 제공하다.
Fang Yongping.
팡용핑.
Suruh Zheng Guoxian
수루 정궈시안
Introduce me to someone.
나를 누군가에게 소개해주세요.
Usually they don't really do that
보통 걔네들은 그렇게 안 하잖아
Contact me directly.
저에게 직접 연락하세요.
Basically everything will pass.
기본적으로 모든 것이 통과됩니다.
Zheng Guoxian.
정궈시안.
Guoxian has been paying attention to me for a long time.
Guoxian은 오랫동안 나에게 관심을 가져 왔습니다.
There's a lot I don't need to say.
말할 필요도 없는 게 많아요.
He will know what to do.
그는 무엇을 해야할지 알 것입니다.
I
나
Just use my power
그냥 내 힘을 써
Come and help him.
와서 그를 도와주세요.
Not just a recommendation.
단순한 추천이 아닙니다.
of.
의.
There are several other cadres here.
여기에는 다른 간부들이 여러 명 있습니다.
then,
그 다음에,
Lifted by my power.
내 힘으로 들어 올려졌습니다.
WHO？
WHO?
Deputy Director of Tetel Group.
Tetel 그룹의 부회장.
Qian Ping.
키안 핑.
including this type.
이 유형도 포함됩니다.
usually,
대개,
they will meet
그들은 만날 것이다
They will make it happen.
그들은 그것을 실현할 것입니다.
For example, in the name of inspection,
예를 들어 검사라는 이름으로
We were given an inside tour.
우리는 내부 견학을 받았습니다.
Involves some internal data.
일부 내부 데이터가 포함됩니다.
wait.
기다리다.
Chen Ting.
첸 팅.
And of course on time.
그리고 물론 정시에.
Give them some profit.
그들에게 약간의 이익을 주세요.
For example, help them buy
예를 들어, 구매를 도와주세요.
servers and others.
서버 및 기타.
the server
서버
Boss Zhang asked me to provide it.
장 상사가 나에게 그것을 제공해달라고 요청했습니다.
then,
그 다음에,
give them
그들에게 줘
for them.
그들을 위해.
Return the money to Ping.
돈을 핑에게 돌려주세요.
10%。
10%。
Qian Ping.
키안 핑.
Ayo.
아요.
Resort Pulau Xiaoyue.
리조트 Pulau Xiaoyue.
Camera on signal tower
시그널 타워의 카메라
Does it have anything to do with you?
당신과 관련이 있나요?
I'm looking for someone
누군가를 찾고 있어요
Find someone to install it.
설치해줄 사람을 찾아보세요.
Anything else?
다른 건 없나요?
There is still one.
아직 하나 있습니다.
A model specially built by the High-Speed ​​Railway Group,
고속철도그룹이 특별히 제작한 모형으로,
I did it too.
나도 그랬어.
This relationship was brokered by Zheng Guoxian.
이 관계는 Zheng Guoxian이 중개했습니다.
that model
그 모델
dikirim ke Jinhai
디키림 케 진하이
Just delivered to Jinhai.
방금 진하이로 배달됐어요.
Express train group.
급행열차군.
What are they planning?
그들은 무엇을 계획하고 있습니까?
who knows.
누가 알아.
I only know
나만 알아요
It seems they are very interested
그 사람들이 관심이 많은 것 같더라고요
High speed rail discounts.
고속철도 할인.
How much do you know about Mr. open?
당신은 이 씨에 대해 얼마나 알고 있나요? 열려 있는?
We can only communicate through games.
우리는 게임을 통해서만 소통할 수 있습니다.
Never seen that.
본 적이 없습니다.
Is he in Zhenhai?
그는 진하이에 있나요?
perhaps.
아마도.
He is very considerate
그는 매우 사려 깊습니다
our actions.
우리의 행동.